My name's Conan Edogawa!
Meu nome é Conan Edogawa!
High school student Shinichi was forced to take a pill that shrunk him!
Forçaram Shinichi, 17 anos, a tomar um comprimido que o encolheu!
Doesn't matter if I'm small!
Não importa eu ser pequeno!
My mind is that of a former great detective,
Minha mente ainda é de um detetive genial,
and my powers of deduction are flawless
e meus poderes de dedução resolvem qualquer caso sem solução!
Valentine's Day is a case of love.
Valentine's Day é um caso de amor.
Who knows, there may be poison in that sweet chocolate!
Pode ter veneno amargo na doçura do chocolate!
The first end of the century in 100 years
O primeiro fim de século em cem anos
When told to cry, I laughed instead
Quando me mandaram chorar, eu ri
The first end of the century in a long, long time
O primeiro fim do século em muito, muito tempo
We're leaping into a wide open world
Estamos saltando rumo a um mundo aberto
The things I tried to understand as a child
As coisas que eu tentava entender quando era criança
remain a mystery even as an adult
Continuam um mistério para mim como adulto
I'm neither a hotshot nor especially great
Não sou um figurão nem grande coisa
All I understand is the pounding of my heart
Eu só entendo as batidas do meu coração
It's neither an answer nor the truth
Não é uma resposta, tampouco a verdade
All I have faith in is the pounding of my heart
Eu só acredito nas batidas do meu coração
That and nothing else
E nada mais
So, what are you going to do, Ran?
Então? O que você vai fazer, Ran?
About what?
Sobre o quê?
Your chocolate for Valentine's Day!
Chocolate para o Valentine's Day!
This huge event only comes once a year, you know!
Esse grande evento só acontece uma vez por ano!
We have to use chocolate to capture men's hearts!
Temos que fazer chocolates que capturem corações!
Oh, right...
Ah, claro...
You're, like, spacing out or something...
Você parece estar no mundo da lua...
Am I?
É mesmo?
Oh! What about him?!
Ah! E ele?
Who's "him"?
Ele quem?
Oh, come on!
Ah, qual é!
Those two guys who tried to pick us up at the coffee shop that one Sunday!
Os dois caras que deram em cima da gente no café no domingo!
Remember?
Lembra?
They said they were both medical students at Beika University!
Eles disseram que fazem medicina na Universidade Beika!
Especially Minagawa-san! He's totally cool!
Principalmente o Minagawa! Ele é tão bacana!
The other one was Wakamatsu-san, was it?
O outro se chamava Wakamatsu, não é mesmo?
He's perfect for you, Ran!
Ele é perfeito pra você, Ran!
He seemed really interested in you, after all!
Ele parecia bem interessado em você!
Hello there, Ran-san! I've been looking for you!
Oi, Ran! Estava te procurando!
What good timing!
Chegou em boa hora!
Don't you agree?
Não concorda?
We'll solve any case at all, no matter how difficult it may be!
Resolvemos qualquer caso, por mais difícil que seja!
If you have any problems, just leave it to us!
Se tiver qualquer problema, pode contar com a gente!
Conan! Stop loafing around and help!
Conan! Pare de ficar à toa e ajude!
I'm high school detective Shinichi Kudo!
Sou Shinichi Kudo, um detetive colegial!
I'm not about to play games with a bunch of pipsqueaks!
Não vou ficar brincando com um bando de pirralhos!
Ran!
Ran!
Ran-san! I'm here today to ask you something important!
Ran, vim pedir uma coisa importante!
Ran-san!
Ran!
I'm here to ask you on a date!
Quer sair comigo?
Date?!
Sair?
Would you come with me to tomorrow's Valentine party?
Quer vir comigo amanhã para a festa de Valentine's Day?
Valentine party?
Festa de Valentine's Day?
Yes. Girls are supposed to give chocolate to a boy they like,
Sim, cada garota dá um chocolate pro garoto de quem gosta,
and if the boy feels the same way for her,
e se for recíproco,
he will eat the chocolate right there on the spot.
o garoto come o chocolate ali mesmo.
Say, will Minagawa-san be coming too?
Ei, o Minagawa também vai?
Of course. The party is taking place at his house, after all.
É claro. Inclusive, a festa vai ser na casa dele.
We'll come! Ran and I will both come for sure!
Nós vamos! A Ran e eu vamos com certeza!
Sonoko!
Sonoko!
R-Really?!
Mesmo?
This is great! Thank you very much!
Que ótimo! Muito obrigado!
Valentine party? Gimme a break.
Festa de Valentine's Day? Dá um tempo.
Well then, I will come pick you up tomorrow.
Bem, nós buscamos vocês amanhã.
Bye!
Tchau!
Why did you say that without asking me?!
Por que você foi dizer aquilo sem me perguntar?
I guess I was right after all.
Acho que eu estava certa.
You like Shinichi-kun, don't you?
Você gosta do Shinichi, não é mesmo?
You're being faithful to him
Está sendo fiel a ele e recusando qualquer outro cara.
Don't be stupid! Who would actually like that big mystery geek?!
Não fala besteira! Quem ia gostar daquele viciado em mistérios?
Well excuse me.
Foi mal por isso.
Then you'll go to the Valentine party, right?
Então você vai para a festa de Valentine's, não vai?
Of course I'll go!
É claro que vou!
Alright! It's decided!
Beleza, está decidido!
Just you watch, Katsuhiko Minagawa!
Fique só vendo, Katsuhiko Minagawa!
I'll use my chocolate to melt even your bone marrow!
Meu chocolate vai te derreter até os ossos!
Sonoko has a new obsession...
A Sonoko tem uma nova obsessão...
Mori Detective Agency
Detetive particular Mori
I'm the great detective Kogoro Mori...
Sou o grande detetive Kogoro Mori...
What are you doing, Ran?
O que você está fazendo, Ran?
Nothing much...
Nada de mais...
It smells like chocolate!
Está com cheiro de chocolate!
Tomorrow's Valentine's Day!
Amanhã é Valentine's Day!
You have someone to give chocolate to then?
Você vai dar chocolate para alguém?
How rude!
Que falta de educação!
I wouldn't be making chocolate by hand if I didn't have someone to give any to!
Eu não prepararia chocolate se não fosse para entregar!
Oh, right! Who knows, Shinichi might just come back!
Ah, verdade! Pode ser que o Shinichi volte!
Shinichi?
Shinichi?
Now that I think about it, there was a guy by that name...
Agora que você falou, tinha mesmo um cara com esse nome...
Hey, now.
Ei, pare com isso.
I'm going now!
Estou indo!
OK. Go and catch a rich man.
Beleza! Pegue um ricaço.
That's weird. Conan-kun isn't here either.
Que estranho. O Conan também não está aqui.
Ran! What're you doing?!
Ran! O que você está fazendo?
We're about to leave without you!
Estamos prestes a ir sem você!
I have no choice but to find out where that chocolate winds up!
Tenho que descobrir onde aquele chocolate está!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Desculpem pela demora!
And away we go!
E lá vamos nós!
Cheers!
Saúde!
Now then, let us introduce our Beika University tennis club
Vamos agora apresentar o clube de tênis da Universidade Beika
to our guests, Ran Mori-san and Sonoko Suzuki-san!
às nossas convidadas, Ran Mori e Sonoko Suzuki!
You go first, Minagawa!
Você primeiro, Minagawa!
OK. I'm Katsuhiko Minagawa, the captain.
Certo. Sou Katsuhiko Minagawa, o capitão.
I'm happy to meet you two.
É um prazer conhecer vocês.
Really?!
Sério?!
I'm happy too!
É um prazer também!
Calm down, calm down...
Se acalme, se acalme.
I'm Kaori Sekiya.
Sou Kaori Sekiya.
Sonoko-san. You're still young, but you shouldn't go overboard like that...
Sonoko, você ainda é jovem, mas é melhor não exagerar assim...
She's envious of me.
Ela tem inveja de mim.
She's really pretty but obviously really jealous too...
Ela é linda, mas está na cara que está com inveja.
Naomichi. You're next.
Naomichi, sua vez.
Come on. You really are gloomy, you know that?
Qual é. Como você é sombrio!
I'm Yoshimi Watanabe. Nice to meet you.
Sou Yoshimi Watanabe. É um prazer.
And then there's me,
E eu,
the strong, yet sensitive, Toshihide Wakamatsu!
o forte, porém sensível, Toshihide Wakamatsu!
Who does Ran think she is?
Quem a Ran pensa que é?
She actually looks like she's having fun.
Parece que ela está se divertindo.
I'm sorry for the wait!
Desculpem pela demora!
Here is today's main dish!
Aqui está o prato principal de hoje!
Thank you ever so much, Mrs. Minagawa!
Muito obrigado, Sra. Minagawa!
You're Minagawa-san's mother?!
Você é a mãe do Minagawa?
You're so young!
Tão jovem!
You certainly know how to flatter a woman!
Você sabe como agradar uma mulher!
Hey, lady! Let's play together!
Moça! Vamos brincar juntos!
Susumu! Go to your room! You're disruptin' the party!
Susumu, volte pro seu quarto! Está atrapalhando a festa!
You're Minagawa-san's younger brother?
Você é o irmãozinho do Minagawa?
You're so cute!
Que gracinha!
But he doesn't really look like Minagawa-san, does he?
Mas ele não se parece com o Minagawa, parece?
How long is that stupid Ran going to be here?!
Até quando a boba da Ran vai ficar aqui?
I'm so cold and hungry!
Estou com frio e fome!
Oh no!
Essa não!
Conan-kun! What are you doing here?!
Conan! O que está fazendo aqui?
I was just going to a friend's house but then I got lost!
Estava na casa de um amigo, mas me perdi!
Do you know that boy?
Você conhece esse garoto?
Yes. He's been staying at my house lately for certain reasons.
Sim, ele está morando na minha casa por algumas circunstâncias.
It must be cold outside. Come in.
Deve estar frio aí fora. Entre.
OK!
Tudo bem!
I think someone should perform something.
Acho que alguém tem que fazer um show.
Naomichi! You do it!
Naomichi, você!
You not hear me or something?! Get this party started!
É surdo por acaso? Faça a festa começar!
I'm not very good at that sort of thing.
Não sou bom nessas coisas.
What?! You dare defy me?!
O quê? Você se atreve a me desafiar?
Just looking at your face makes me sick!
Passo mal só de olhar pra sua cara!
Don't you think Minagawa-san's got a bit of an attitude problem?
Não acha o Minagawa meio malvado?
It's good for guys to be a little like that!
É bom que rapazes sejam um pouco assim!
Anyway, did you bring your chocolate?!
Enfim, você trouxe o chocolate?
Yeah...
Sim.
Watch! Minagawa-san's down for the count once he eats my chocolate!
Fique só vendo! O Minagawa está prestes a comer o meu chocolate!
You sure you didn't put poison in it then?
Você não o envenenou?
I, Sonoko Suzuki, humbly offer--
Eu, Sonoko Suzuki, ofereço humildemente...
Say, beautiful girls like you
Ei, meninas bonitas como você devem gostar
must have hobbies like tea ceremony and flower arrangement, right?
de cerimônia do chá e flores, né?
Karate.
Karatê.
How could Ran-san do anything so uncivilized?!
Como que a Ran poderia fazer algo tão bruto?
Karate.
Karatê.
As if such a lovely and charming woman would ever be into karate!
Até parece que uma mulher adorável e charmosa assim gostaria de karatê!
Kaori.
Kaori.
Stop treating Naomichi like that.
Pare de tratar o Naomichi assim.
It really pisses me off when you feel sorrier for him than me!
Me irrita quando você sente mais pena dele do que de mim!
You mean to say you're worse off than him?
Está dizendo que você é pior que ele?
What?!
O quê?!
You've changed!
Você mudou!
You've become so reckless ever since then!
Ficou tão imprudente desde então!
What do you know?!
O que você sabe, afinal?
I know enough! We grew up together, after all!
O bastante! Afinal, nós crescemos juntos!
Get a hold of yourself!
Controle-se!
Will you accept this?
Você aceita?
Knock it off. I only want to be friends.
Pare com isso. Só quero amizade.
I see...
Entendi...
I guess you really do like Yoshimi the best...
Parece que você gosta mesmo da Yoshimi...
What's the matter?
O que foi?
It should be OK, right? It's just her hand...
Não tem problema, tem? É só a mão dela...
Here goes!
Lá vai!
I have to take the initiative!
Eu tenho que tomar a iniciativa!
What lovely hands...
Que mãos adoráveis...
Ran-san!
Ran!
Outta the way!
Sai da frente!
Conan-kun!
Conan!
R-Ran-san!
Ran!
Yes?
Sim?
Take that!
Toma essa!
Freakin' kid!
Pirralho endiabrado!
Stay away from Ran!
Fique longe da Ran!
Conan-kun!
Conan!
Susumu! How many times do I have to tell you?!
Susumu, quantas vezes eu tenho que dizer?
No sweets! Your cavity still hasn't healed yet!
Nada de doces! Sua cárie ainda está se curando!
But Kaori gave it to me!
Mas a Kaori me deu!
Kaori.
Kaori.
It was Katsuhiko, wasn't it?!
Foi o Katsuhiko, não foi?
Did he do something bad to you?
Ele fez alguma coisa com você?
It's none of your business!
Não é da sua conta!
Katsuhiko's nothing but human scum!
O Katsuhiko é um lixo!
There's no reason for him to hurt you like that, no matter what!
Não tem por que ele a machucar desse jeito, não importa o motivo!
Just leave me alone!
Me deixe em paz!
Damn that Katsuhiko!
Katsuhiko maldito!
Go Minagawa-san!
Vai, Minagawa!
Katsuhiko! It's 10 years too soon for you to challenge me!
Katsuhiko, espere uns dez anos para ter chance contra mim!
Ran-san must be sick of being with a guy with muscle for brains.
A Ran deve estar cansada de ficar com um cara que pensa com os músculos.
Minagawa! Are you lookin' for a fight?!
Minagawa, quer brigar, é?
I just call it like I see it.
Só estou dizendo o que vejo.
What?!
O quê?!
You're always like this!
Você sempre foi assim!
Why not think about other people's feelings for once?!
Que tal pensar no sentimento dos outros pra variar?
You mean you have feelings too?
Está insinuando que você também tem sentimentos?
Why, you...
Maldito...
Now, now, that's enough!
Ei, já chega!
How about something to work off that alcohol?
Que tal algo para diluir o álcool?
Let go!
Solta!
Say, Katsuhiko...
Ei, Katsuhiko...
What?! You gonna lecture me too?!
O que foi? Vai me dar sermão também?
I would never.
Eu não ia fazer isso.
Now then, let's all have dessert!
Ei, vamos comer a sobremesa!
Ah, here it is! Mrs. Minagawa's home-made cakes!
Era isso que eu queria! Os bolos da Sra. Minagawa!
I hope you like them...
Espero que gostem...
Of course I will! Thank you!
Claro que vou gostar! Obrigado!
Say, is that cake good?
Ei, o bolo está bom?
Both the cake and the coffee are great!
O bolo e o café estão ótimos!
Bitter!
Que amargo!
Don't drink her coffee!
Não beba o café da moça!
Here! Have some cake!
Aqui está! Pegue um bolinho!
Katsuhiko. Aren't you going to eat your cake?
Katsuhiko, não vai comer o seu bolo?
No. I hate sweets.
Não, odeio doces.
Don't you think maybe you're smoking too much?
Não acha que está fumando demais?
You should try to cut back a little.
Melhor tentar maneirar um pouco.
Get off my case and quit annoyin' me!
Pare de encher meu saco!
Looks like I got a little drunk.
Acho que fiquei meio bêbado.
Think I'll go get some fresh air.
Vou tomar um ar fresco.
Empty.
Vazio.
You can have mine.
Pode pegar o meu.
Yoshimi likes him after all...
Sabia, a Yoshimi gosta dele...
What does she see in him, I wonder?
O que será que ela vê nele?
Which reminds me, do you have any chocolate for me, Ran-san?
Falando nisso, você trouxe chocolate para mim, Ran?
It's Katsuhiko! He's...
É o Katsuhiko! Ele...
K-Katsuhiko! Katsuhiko!
Katsuhiko!
Call for the police and an ambulance!
Chamem a polícia e uma ambulância!
Right!
Certo.
Katsuhiko!
Katsuhiko!
Mrs. Minagawa...
Sra. Minagawa...
Katsuhiko-san passed away earlier.
O Katsuhiko faleceu agora há pouco.
The cause appears to be agricultural chemicals used as food poison.
Parece que a causa foram agrotóxicos usados como veneno.
Yoshimi Watanabe-san.
Yoshimi Watanabe.
He collapsed shortly after eating your chocolate, did he not?
Ele caiu logo depois de comer o seu chocolate, não?
Yes.
Sim.
It goes without saying that this case is an easy one.
Nem preciso dizer que é um caso fácil.
What are you doing here?!
O que está fazendo aqui?!
I, the great detective Kogoro Mori, hastened to the scene!
então eu, o grande detetive Kogoro Mori, vim correndo!
You did it!
Foi você!
You poisoned the chocolate in order to kill the victim!
Você envenenou o chocolate para matar a vítima!
Romantic issues were your motive!
Seu motivo: questões românticas!
All we have to do is check the rest of your chocolate to prove it!
É só testar o que sobrou do chocolate para comprovar!
No! It wasn't me!
Não, não fui eu!
Yoshimi!
Yoshimi!
Everything's too convenient for it to have been her.
Está tudo conveniente demais para ter sido ela.
Everyone's eaten the exact same things as the victim.
Todo mundo comeu exatamente as mesmas coisas que a vítima.
Even if the sushi was poisoned,
Mesmo se o sushi estivesse envenenado, não tem como saber quem comeria.
Everyone drank coffee that came from the same pot.
Todo mundo tomou café da mesma cafeteira.
Which means it was the cake?
Ou seja, foi o bolo?
No, the victim didn't eat it!
Não, a vítima não comeu o bolo!
No. I hate sweets.
Não, odeio doces.
What does it all mean?
O que isso quer dizer?
Was Yoshimi-san the murderer after all?!
Foi mesmo a Yoshimi?
That's it!
É isso!
Mister!
Moço!
Come to think of it,
Pensando nisso, tinha uma bituca de cigarro na cena do crime, não?
A cigarette?
Cigarro?
That's right! That's a possibility too!
Isso mesmo! Também é possível!
So this is the cigarette butt discovered at the scene of the crime.
Então essa é a bituca encontrada na cena do crime.
Yes, there are ways to poison cigarettes...
Sim, tem como envenenar cigarros...
I saw it! When Minagawa-san went outside,
Eu vi! Quando o Minagawa saiu,
Naomichi-san gave him his cigarettes!
o Naomichi deu os cigarros para ele!
N-Naomichi! How could you?!
Naomichi! Como você pôde?
Well?!
Então?
We can always find out if we examine the cigarette butt, you know!
Dá para saber se investigarmos a bituca!
It's true! I did it!
É verdade! Fui eu!
I've hated him for a long time!
Eu sempre o odiei!
That damn Katsuhiko was always making a fool of me!
O desgraçado do Katsuhiko sempre me fazia de bobo!
He even hurt Kaori!
Ele até machucou a Kaori!
The filter?
No filtro?
No! He didn't do it!
Não, não foi ele!
Mommy! My tooth hurts!
Mamãe, meu dente tá doendo!
She's washing the coffee cups.
Ela está lavando as xícaras de café.
At a time like this?
Em um momento destes?
That's it! I got it!
É isso! Já sei!
Here goes!
Lá vai!
I call this the Anesthetic Watch Gun.
Esta é a arma anestésica.
With it, you can make anyone within close range go to sleep instantly.
Com ela, dá para pôr qualquer pessoa próxima para dormir na hora.
His voice was Number 59, if I remember correctly...
Se não me engano, a voz dele é a 59...
One moment, please, Inspector Megure.
Espere um pouco, detetive Megure.
He is not the murderer.
Ele não é o assassino.
What are you talking about? He's confessed to it, you know.
O que você está dizendo? Ele confessou.
He did indeed plan to murder the victim, but he failed.
Ele pretendia mesmo matar a vítima, mas não conseguiu.
Have a look at the cigarette butt.
Dê uma olhada na bituca.
All of the victim's other cigarettes in the house were unfiltered.
Todos os outros cigarros da vítima não tinham filtro.
After receiving the cigarettes from Naomichi,
Depois de receber os cigarros do Naomichi,
the victim removed the filter before lighting one up.
a vítima tirou o filtro antes de acender.
In other words, he didn't smoke the part that had the poison in it.
Ou seja, ele não fumou a parte que tinha veneno.
Then who did it, Dad?!
Então quem foi, pai?
The real murderer was...
O verdadeiro assassino foi...
...you, Katsuhiko-kun's mother!
...você, mãe do Katsuhiko!
What are you talking about?!
O que está dizendo?!
How in the world could I have done it?!
Como eu poderia ter feito isso?
By poisoning the food.
Envenenando a comida.
Everyone ate the same food!
Todo mundo comeu a mesma comida!
Yes. But only Katsuhiko-kun died.
Sim, mas só o Katsuhiko morreu.
He died because he didn't eat.
Ele morreu porque não comeu.
What do you mean, he didn't eat?
Como assim, não comeu?
Mrs. Minagawa.
Sra. Minagawa.
I hear you were nearly red with anger
Soube que você ficou vermelha de raiva
when Susumu-kun ate some chocolate.
quando o Susumu comeu o chocolate.
Yet you let him have some cake!
Mesmo assim, você deixou que ele comesse o bolo!
Why was that?
Por que isso?
It was because you put poison in the coffee
Porque você pôs veneno no café
and the antidote in the cake!
e o antídoto no bolo!
Seeing Susumu-kun drink the poisoned coffee,
Ao ver que o Susumu bebeu o café envenenado,
you rushed to give him some of the cake and the antidote!
você correu para dar um pouco do bolo com o antídoto!
You knew that Katsuhiko-kun probably wouldn't eat the cake
Você sabia que o Katsuhiko não comeria o bolo
since he hated sweets.
porque ele odiava doces.
Then, upon devising this plan,
Então, ao elaborar o plano,
you decided to use the fact that Yoshimi-san loved him to your advantage!
você se aproveitou do fato da Yoshimi gostar dele!
You knew without question that he would eat her chocolate.
Você sabia que ele comeria o chocolate dela sem falta.
Being the very first person on the scene,
Sendo a primeira pessoa no local,
you took the chocolate he partially ate
você pegou o chocolate que ele tinha mordido
and replaced it with poisoned chocolate!
e o substituiu pelo chocolate envenenado!
All while trying to make Yoshimi-san look guilty, of course.
Tudo para que a Yoshimi fosse vista como culpada, é claro.
Pure fiction! There's no proof!
Isso é pura ficção! Você não tem provas!
But there is. In the coffee cups.
Tenho, sim. As xícaras de café.
Before the police came, you washed the coffee cups as quickly as possible.
Antes da polícia chegar, você lavou as xícaras o mais rápido que pôde.
No matter how much you washed them,
Por mais que as tenha lavado,
detailed examination will still find the poison!
um exame minucioso detectará vestígios de veneno!
Even if there isn't any left in the cups,
Mesmo que não tenha nada nas xícaras,
there will still be some in the drain pipes.
ainda terá um pouco nos canos.
Mrs. Minagawa.
Sra. Minagawa.
It appears it's starting to melt.
Parece que está começando a derreter.
Yoshimi-san's real chocolate bar, which you hid in your kimono, that is.
A barra de chocolate que a Yoshimi deu e que você escondeu no quimono.
Nonsense!
Que absurdo!
How would I know that he would eat Yoshimi's chocolate?!
Como eu saberia que ele ia comer o chocolate da Yoshimi?
Why would I kill my own son?!
Por que eu mataria meu próprio filho?
No! Katsuhiko's real parents died 7 years ago in an accident!
Não! Os verdadeiros pais dele morreram há sete anos num acidente!
Then you, his father's sister, took him in!
Então você, a irmã do pai dele, o acolheu!
Katsuhiko liked Yoshimi because she looked like his real mother.
Katsuhiko gostava da Yoshimi pois ela se parecia com a mãe de verdade dele.
That's how you knew for sure that he would eat her chocolate!
Por isso você sabia que ele comeria o chocolate dela!
I'm so sorry, Yoshimi-san!
Desculpe, Yoshimi!
I just happened to see you buying chocolate one day
Eu a vi comprando chocolate no outro dia por acaso
and then the idea suddenly came to me!
e a ideia me veio à cabeça!
I had no other choice!
Eu não tive escolha!
We desperately needed Katsuhiko's inheritance
Precisávamos da herança do Katsuhiko
because my husband's business went under!
porque a empresa do meu marido faliu!
I wanted to protect this house and Susumu's happiness!
Eu quero proteger esta família e a felicidade do Susumu!
Just my imagination
Só impressão minha
Playing with threads around my finger while drinking lukewarm tea
Brincando com fios entre os dedos bebendo chá morno
Let's walk lightly to the bossa nova rhythm
Vamos caminhar levianamente ao ritmo da bossa nova
The puzzle pieces are in my hands
As peças de quebra-cabeça em minhas mãos
That's right...
Isso mesmo...
I was in the same place last week but with different clothes
Semana passada eu estava no mesmo lugar, mas com roupas diferentes
Step by step, there's no reason to be anxious
Passo a passo, não tem por que ficar ansioso
Case by case, I don't care if you laugh
Caso a caso, tudo bem se você rir
Beyond the countless days, she's waiting for me
Além dos dias incontáveis, ela espera por mim
I gotta go my own way
Tenho que seguir meu próprio caminho
A lot sure happened today...
Aconteceu tanta coisa hoje...
What should I do with this chocolate now?
O que faço com este chocolate agora?
Ran-san! Here you are!
Ran, aqui está você!
I could give you a ride home if you want...
Eu posso te dar carona para casa...
No, that's okay...
Não, não precisa...
Oh! Is that chocolate for me?!
Ah! É chocolate para mim?
No--
Não...
Thank you! I'm utterly delighted!
Obrigado! É um prazer!
That's enough!
Já chega!
Just leave me alone!
Me deixe em paz!
I'm sorry for bothering you!
Desculpe por te incomodar!
For Shinichi-kun
Para Shinichi
Ran...
Ran...
You can eat it if you'd like.
Pode comer, se quiser.
I'm sure Shinichi wouldn't mind either.
Sei que o Shinichi não se importaria.
You followed me to keep me safe, right?
Você me seguiu para me proteger, não foi?
Thanks!
Obrigada!
Sending 25 million yen along with toys seems too much to be a prank.
Enviar 25 milhões de ienes com os brinquedos como trote é exagero.
And that letter... What does it say they're coming for?!
E a carta... O que quer dizer "Estou indo"?
Great work, Shinichi!
Ótimo trabalho, Shinichi!
It was nothing--
Não foi nada...
On the next Conan--
Presentes Mensais Ameaçadores
Next Conan's Hint:
Dica do próximo Conan:
Barcode.
Código de barras.
Next episode's case is a little extra difficult!
O próximo é meio difícil.